<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Shirley Shu</title>
    <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Shirley Shu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ssjshirley.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Deployment Triggers</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</guid>
      <description>Addressed pretty significant page load performance issue founde in larger deployments. Eliminates uses of intensive backend query, replacing it with an asynchronous API call against a lucene index. This change reduces page load from from 2+ minutes to nearly instant, with an incredibly responsive UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MM-QUIC: A mobility-aware multipath QUIC for satellite networks</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/publications/mmquic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/publications/mmquic/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The Integrated Terrestrial and LEO satellite network (ITSN) is promising for providing ubiquitous communication services. In ITSN, network mobility brings new challenges and attracts attention. In this paper, we promote a new transport layer protocol, Multipath QUIC (MPQUIC) to deal with the network mobility issue in ITSN. ITSN is characterized by high bandwidth delay product (BDP). The standard congestion control algorithm of MPQUIC, Opportunistic Linked Increases Algorithm (OLIA), encounters great challenges such as congestion window (cwnd) overshooting whenever handoff, which motivates our proposal, a Mobility-aware Multipath QUIC (MM-QUIC) congestion control algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Quick UDP Internet Connection (QUIC) Protocol</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/publications/quictalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/publications/quictalk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Added Docker Build Status Badge to shields.io</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</guid>
      <description>Shields.io is a massive library of badges that can be inserted into project README&amp;rsquo;s or websites displaying various statuses (code coverage, health, version, etc). Support for docker was missing the current build health, and was a pretty trivial addition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema.org Structured Data documentation fixes</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/contributions/schema-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/contributions/schema-org/</guid>
      <description>While adding Structured Data to a client&amp;rsquo;s website I found some example JSON that was invalid. Simple contribution to cleanup the user documentation providing syntactically valid JSON documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forcing Visits to use SSL</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Intro Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter whether it&amp;rsquo;s a CakePHP app for a client, your own personal CMS, or any other web based application. If your passing around passwords or other sensitive info you should really implement SSL. SSL provides 2 main perks to your visitors.
 First it encrypts all communication that flies across the web. This prevents curious or devious billies from getting your secrets. Secondly it ensures to the user that your server is in fact who it claims, and not a nasty &amp;lsquo;man in the middle&amp;rdquo; attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain based Criminal Records Database</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/creations/blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/creations/blockchain/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multipath QUIC Protocol Design</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/creations/mpquic-ns3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/creations/mpquic-ns3/</guid>
      <description>Design a multipath QUIC protocol on ns-3 based on the theorem of MPTCP and QUIC. Realized majority functions of QUIC protocol over a socket based network system, written in C++. Research on the performance with various combination of transmission types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predict Hotel Type in Expedia</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/creations/predicthotel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/projects/creations/predicthotel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://ssjshirley.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssjshirley.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;JSON&amp;quot;]  Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>